#大家好 你看 我弟帶回來的小狗
Hi everyone! Look! These are the puppies brought by my younger brother.
#那麼多
So many!
#七條
Seven!
#還是好小的 剛斷奶的
Still very small. They've just weaned.
#你看 剛 剛斷完奶他就把它帶回來了
Look. He, he brought them back right after they've weaned.
#現在都會走路了
Now they can walk.
#前幾天還不會走路哦 帶回來
They couldn't a few days ago, when they were just brought here.
#這不知道叫 這個不知道叫甚麼狗來的
I don't know, I don't know what dogs they are.
#嘴巴好大
They have large mouths.
#你看這個
Look at this one!
#也很漂亮這個
It's also pretty.
#花的
It's brown and white.
#你看這小狗
Look at the puppies!
#好乖
They're so nice.
#這條花的比較喜歡我
The one in black and white likes me more.
#黑的比較
And the black one,
#喜歡攝影小哥
likes Mr. Cameraman more.
#你看 這個小黃狗
Look! This brown puppy.
#它嘴巴好大啊 這個
It's mouth is very large.
#你們也要提是不是
Do you guys want to be taken up too?
#好 等一下 排著隊來提啊
Alright! A moment! Queue up!
#那麼喜 那麼喜歡我提你們
You all, you all like it so much when I hold you up.
#很漂亮的哦 這個小狗
It's really pretty, this puppy.
#拎著它都不動
It's not moving when I'm holding it.
#誰還要提的
Who's next?
#這個最小 這個
This is the smallest, this one,
#最漂亮這個
and the prettiest.
#這個是
He's a,
#小公狗
little boy.
#你看它的嘴巴 好大啊 它嘴吧
Look at his mouth. His mouth is really large.
#哎呦 摔它一跤
Ayo! He slips.
#你看這個稍微小的樣子
Look! This one seems to be a bit smaller.
#現在都瘦了
They're now skinny.
#天天給它牛奶給它喝
We give them milk everyday.
#小花 (註︰這個真不知道甚麼譯，英文應該沒有「花紋」這個概念的簡單說法)
Little colourful
#這個很靚哦這個 它毛好白啊
This is really beautiful. The hair is so pure and white.
#比較愛乾淨
It likes cleanliness.
#小狗
Puppy!
#這黑的
This is black,
#那麼小 那麼黑
so small, so black.
#好靚啊
It's beautiful.
#你看 它們都排著據
Look! They're all queuing up,
#排著隊 站在這裡
queuing up, standing here,
#想 想讓我拎一下它
hoping, hoping to be taken up.
#啊 啊 好 好
Oh, oh, okay, okay.
#我拎一下你
Just a while.
#舒不舒服 拎得
Does it feel good, in my hand?
#很舒服是不是
Wonderful, isn't it?
#等一下我給你餵奶粉要不要
You'll be having milk powder. Do you like it?
#要不要
Do you?
#等下我搞點奶粉來給它喝一下
Let me give them some milk powder.
#它這個眼神
Look at its eyes.
#是不是很糾結 是不是
The eyes look perplexed, don't they?
#不是 哦
No? You say no?
#它的嘴巴
Its mouth,
#它嘴巴好好看啊 它嘴巴
Its mouth is so nice, the mouth.
#開飯啦 開飯啦 開飯啦
Meal time, meal time, meal time!
#好啦 今天的視頻到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
#它們都好餓啦
They're all starving.
#我等下餵一下它們
We need to feed them now.
#來啦 就這樣 可以 就這樣
Come on! Here! Yea! It's fine!